[
  {
    "Question": "Where does Howard say he'll fly Ava after the successful flight of Hercules?",
    "A": "Paris",
    "B": "London",
    "C": "California",
    "D": "Ireland",
    "Answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which character in the movie is played by Leonardo Dicaprio?",
    "A": "Noah",
    "B": "Howard",
    "C": "Ava",
    "D": "Howard Sr.",
    "Answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What was the plan 'Hercules' originally designed for?",
    "A": "Passengers",
    "B": "Military",
    "C": "For fun",
    "D": "Medical",
    "Answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What airline did Howard buy a controlling interest in?",
    "A": "Tran Air",
    "B": "US Air",
    "C": "TWA",
    "D": "Southwest",
    "Answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What disorder did Howard Hughes suffer from?",
    "A": "Multiple Personality",
    "B": "Bipolar",
    "C": "Depression",
    "D": "Obessive Compulsive Disorder",
    "Answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Howard has 2 crashes, his first crash was in a field of what?",
    "A": "Wheat",
    "B": "Corn",
    "C": "Beets",
    "D": "Hay",
    "Answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Is this movie based on a true story?",
    "A": "Yes",
    "B": "No",
    "C": "Maybe",
    "D": "I Don't Know",
    "Answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In what time period did this movie take place?",
    "A": "1910-1915",
    "B": "1920-1940",
    "C": "1950",
    "D": "1960-1976",
    "Answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Howard Hughes was known as a record breaking, high risk industrialist womanizer.",
    "A": "True",
    "B": "False",
    "C": "Maybe",
    "D": "I Don't Know",
    "Answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "Question": "'Some men dream the future, he built it' This quote is referring to who?",
    "A": "Leonardo Dicaprio",
    "B": "Roland Sweet",
    "C": "Howard Hughes",
    "D": "Noah Dietrich",
    "Answer": "C"
  }
]